Guide to the Alexander M. Drummond papers, 1917-1956.
Drummond, Alexander M. papers, 1917-1956
- Series IV. Teaching and Professorship
  - Cornell Dramatic Club Tickets, ca. 1917 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Ushers Ribbon, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's (Box 6, Folder 42)
    fragile mounts
  - Cornell Play reviews and a few Ithaca College reviews, 1935 - 1936 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Documents, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Newsletters; Correspondence; Finances; etc
  - Departmental Papers, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Department of Public Speaking and Dramatics Newsletters
  - Master Copies of Reading Lists for Various Courses, 1940 - 1949 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Lists of Public Speaking Books, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Phonetic, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Sentences for use with the Telegraphone
  - Cornell Memorabilia, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cornell Reunion Programs, 1948 - 1949 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Cornell Junior Week Booklets, 1947 - 1948 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Cornell University Theatre Correspondence, 1947 - 1948, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Course 42 Participation Survey, May, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Set Design Sketches, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Lewis
  - Checklist of Plays, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Suggestions for Advanced Study, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Fabric Samples, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Record Book of Prop and Costume Inventories, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - New York State English Council, May, 1951 - May, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Misc. Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Notes on Theatre, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Grants and Fundraising, 1940 - 1944 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Set Design Sketch, undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
    Marvels of the Midway
  - Notes on The Province of Philology, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - AETA, 1937 - 1954 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    Post-war Education; Newsletters; Children's Theatre; Correspondence (Divided into 3 folders)
  - ANTA - 1, 1947 - 1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Newsletters; Service pamphlets; Conference schedules; By-laws; Album; History
  - ANTA - 2, 1947 - 1951 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Newsletters; Correspondence (Divided into two folders)
  - ANTA - 3, 1946 - 1954 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    The Southwest Review; Structure; History; National Theatre Conference
  - ANTA - 4, 1949 - 1951 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Congressional resolution to establish a national Theatre, Opera and Ballet; Other correspondence
  - National Theatre Conference, 1933 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Newsletters; Rules and Regulations; Correspondence; War-time theatre
  - National Theatre Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - National Theatre Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre Conference, 1947- 1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Meeting and conference minutes; Newsletters; Correspondence; Member lists
  - National Theatre Conference, 1938 - 1946 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Conference reports; Book reviews; Notes; Statistics; Finances; Royalties
  - National Theatre Conference, 1934 - 1946 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    USO programs; Yearly Reports; Finances; Constitution; Regulations
  - National Theatre Conference, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Armed Forces Institute Project
  - National Association of Teachers of Speech, 1915 - 1944 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    National convention; Newsletter
  - New York Community Theatre Association, 1943 - 1954 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Annual meeting program; Newsletters; NY State Speech Association; University theatre
  - Community Theatre Bulletins, Little Theatre Bulletins and NY State Speech Association, 1941 - 1950 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    (Divided into two folders)
  - New York State Theatre Conference, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - NCTE Committee on Playlist, 1953 - 1954 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Possible Plays for Cornell Volume of Plays, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Tentative Casting (etc.) for Plays, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Children's Theatre, 1948 - 1949 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Cornell Home Economics; Puppets; AETA Children's Theatre Conference; and more
  - Carnival Caravan, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - College Theatre Congressional Bill, 1949 - 1940 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Festival of Contemporary Arts, 1945 - 1954 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Library Information, 1941 - 1942 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Book lists; Catalogues; Order forms
  - Western Canada Theatre Conference, 1942 - 1946 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Williamsburg, VA Theatre and Reconstruction Plans, 1944 - 1947 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Personal correspondence; Newspaper articles; First Theatre notes and pictures; Blueprints
  - Cornell Show, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Script
- Series V. Photographs and Glass Slides
  - Photographs, Prints, and Images of Drummond, Theatre and various other individuals, 1923 - 1955 (Box 8)
    Many Barrett Gallagher prints, research material, family photographs, portraits of Drummond, theater set and plays, Cornell photo.
  - 57 slides depicting mostly panoramas with corresponding description and information on note cards, undated (Box 22)
  - Aaron Slick From Punkin Crick photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Accent on Youth photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning photographs negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Across the Continent photograph negatives, January 9 - 17, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ah Wilderness photograph negatives, May 9 - 10, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Alice in Wonderland photograph negatives, Spring 1922 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Freshman women
  - Alice in Wonderland photograph negatives, April 21, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Gallagher
  - Alice in Wonderland photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Alison's House photograph negatives, January 19, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Among the Breakers photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Anatol photograph negatives, April 15 - 22, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Angel Street photograph negatives, August, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Another Language photograph negatives, January 12 - 13, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Antique Shop photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Apartment 3-D photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Heerman's One act and NY State Plays
  - Aria de Capo photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Arms and the Man photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Around the Corner photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace photograph negatives, December 2 - 4, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - As You Like It photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    modern dress
  - As You Like It photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    costumes
  - The Accent of F-6 photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Awake and Sing photograph negatives, May, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - The Barretts of Wimpole Street photograph negatives, October 30, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Beautiful People photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Beautiful People photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Beauty and the Beast photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Beyond the Horizon photograph negatives, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Beyond the Horizon photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - The Bishop's Candlesticks photograph negatives, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Kermis one-act
  - Blithe Spirit photograph negatives, January 15 - February 7, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Bonds of Interest photograph negatives, February 1, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - The Boar photograph negatives, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - John Gabriel Borkman photograph negatives, April 21 - May 5, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Box and Cox photograph negatives, March 3 - 4, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Boy Meets Girl photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - The Breadwinner photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Brief Music photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Bucktails photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Bugles at Noon photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Come Away, Death photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
    British one-act
  - Candida photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Cardiff Giant photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Cardiff Giant photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Charley's Aunt photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Chenango Crone photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - The Chief Thing photograph negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - A Child Is Born photograph negatives, December, 1919 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - The Circle photograph negatives, February 17, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Clear All Wires photograph negatives, January 12 - 19, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - The Contrast glass negatives, November 19 - 21, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Contrast glass negatives, November 19 - 21, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - The Critic glass negative, March 11 - 12, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - The Damask Cheek photograph negatives, Summer Session, November 20 - 23, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - A Day in the Vineyard photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Deep Are the Roots photograph negatives, April 28 - 30, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Desire Under the Elms photograph negatives, February, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Detour photograph negatives, August 3 - 4, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Doctor Knock photograph negatives, May 12 - 14, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Dollar Delirium photograph negatives, May 11 - 12, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Enemy of the People glass and film negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Emperor Jones photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - An Enemy of the People photograph negatives, March 5, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - An Enemy of the People photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Enemy of the People photograph negatives, March 23 - 24, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Escape photograph negatives, April 14, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Etiquette photograph negatives, Summer, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Evening Dress Indispensable photograph negatives, October 7, 14, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Everyman photograph negatives, December 18, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Excursion photograph negatives, January 23, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Fair Day Thursday photograph negatives, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Heerman's one-act
  - Family Reunion photograph negatives, April, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Fancy Free photograph negatives, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    one-act
  - The Far-off Hills photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Farm and Home Week photograph negatives, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Farm and Home Week photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Farm and Home Week photograph negatives, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Farm and Home Week photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Farm and Home Week photograph negatives, probably 1936 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Fashion photograph negatives, November 22 - 23, December 7, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - First Lady photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Fishin' Weather photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Four - H Plays photograph negatives, June, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Fumed Oak photograph negatives, January 7 - 8, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - George and Margaret photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Girls in Uniform photograph negatives, November 9, 16, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - The Glass Menagerie photograph negatives, October 15, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - HMS Pinafore photograph negatives, December 14 - 15, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - HMS Pinafore photograph negatives, March, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Happy Birthday photograph negatives, December 8 - 10, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Happy Journey photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Hay Fever photograph negatives, November 11, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Hay Fever photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    With Wells College
  - Headin' for Havana photograph negatives, March 13 - 14, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Heartbreak House photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Hello, Out There photograph negatives, October 7, 14, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Hello, Out There photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Heerman's one acts, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Heerman's one acts, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Holiday photograph negatives, October 25 - 26, November 2, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Home and Beauty photograph negatives, Summer Session, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Honeymoon Niagara Falls photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - The Hope Chest photograph negatives, August 4 - 5, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - How He Lied to Her Husband photograph negatives, December, 1955, January, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Hullabaloo photograph negatives, May 7 - 8, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Ile photograph negatives, October 21 - 22, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Idyll on a Summer Hotel Porch photograph negatives, undated (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest photograph negatives, July 20 - 21, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest photograph negatives, October, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest glass negatives, February 5 - 6, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest glass negatives, February 5 - 6, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest glass and photograph negatives, February 5 - 6, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest glass negatives, February 5 - 6, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The Importance of Being Ernest glass negatives, February 5 - 6, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - An Inspector Calls photograph negatives, March 17 - 19, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Is Life Worth Living photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - It Can't Happen Here photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Joan of Lorraine photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Jim Dandy photograph negatives, February 6 - 7 and March 6 - 7, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Jumpin' the Broom photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Juno and the Paycock photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    From Abbey Theatre
  - Kermis One-act photograph negatives, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Kind Lady photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Life of John Doe photograph negatives, March 9, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Ladies in Retirement photograph negatives, August 8 - 9 and November 14 - 15, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Ladies in Retirement photograph negatives, August 6 - 7, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Ladies in Waiting photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - The Late Christopher Bean photograph negatives, November 24 and December 7 - 8, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Leave it to Psmith photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Let's Get on With the Marrying photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    Heerman's and NY State one-act
  - The Life of John Doe photograph negatives, February 11 - 12, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Louder Please photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Love in '76 photograph negatives, May 1 - 2, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Macbeth photograph negatives, February 4 - 5, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Madwoman of Chaillot photograph negatives, December, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - The Male Animal photograph negatives, June 13 - 14, October 24 - 25, November 7-8, August 1-2, 1941, various (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - The Man in the Bowler Hat glass negatives, March 12 - 13, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - The Man in the Bowler Hat photograph negatives, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Materia Medica photograph negatives, August 4 - 5, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - A Matter of Husbands photograph negatives, January 7 - 8, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - The Mayor and the Manicure photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - A Midsummer Nights' Dream glass negatives, April 23 - 23, 29 - 30, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - The Mikado photograph negatives, January 12 - 13, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - The Mikado photograph negative, undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Mied Oats photograph negatives, December 1944, December 1945 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Mill Town photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
    NY State one-act
  - Mixin' Up the Rent photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Monday photograph negatives, February 19 - 20, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Morning's at 7 photograph negatives, undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Mr. Pim Passes By photograph negatives, July 22 - 23, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Morn to Midnight photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Murder is Fun photograph negatives, November, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Music Hall Show photograph negatives, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Night Must Fall photograph negatives, May 21 - 22 and June 11 - 12, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Nine Girls photograph negatives, January and March, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - No Mother to Guide Her photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Nothing Doing photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Of Mice and Men photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Once Upon a Hill photograph negatives, December, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Once Upon a Hill photograph negatives, Spring 1946 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Our Good Brother Joseph photograph negatives, May 11 - 12, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Our Lean Years photograph negatives, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Our Town photograph negatives, May and June, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Our Town photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Outward Bound photograph negatives, Summer Session, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Outward Bound photograph negatives, 1945 - 1946 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Playgoers photograph negatives, December 4, 6, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Philadelphia Diary photograph negatives, March 4 - 6, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - The Pigeon photograph negatives, April 24 - 26, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Pirates of Penzance photograph negatives, March, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Plain Folks photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - The Playboy of the Western World photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - The Play's the Thing photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - The Play's The Thing photograph negatives, April 20 - 22, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - A Pound on Demand photograph negatives, Summer Session, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Princess Ida photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Private Lives photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Privilege and Privation photograph negatives, March, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Pullman Car Hiawatha photograph negatives, February 19 - 20, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Pyramus and Thisbe photograph negatives, May 7 - 8, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Quiet Facing the Park photograph negatives, December, 1944 and January, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - The Queen's Husband photograph negatives, November 10, 16, 17, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Rappings and Table Movings photograph negatives, May, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Rehearsal photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Riders to the Sea photograph negatives, December 4, 6, 1919 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Romeo and Juliet photograph negatives, February, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - R.U.R photograph negatives, December 4 - 7, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - School for Wives photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - The Second Shepherd's Play photograph negatives, December 12, 15, 16, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - See Naples and Die photograph negatives, December 8 - 9, 1933 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Shall We Join the Ladies? photograph negatives, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - She Stoops to Conquer photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - The Silver Card photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Six Characters photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Skin of Our Teeth photograph negatives, May 26, and June 1, 8, 9, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Slope of a Hill photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Sparkin' photograph negatives, April 10 - 11, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Spring photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Springtime for Henry photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Squaring the Circle photograph negatives, October 18 - 19, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - The Star-Wagon photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Summer and Smoke photograph negatives, February, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Sunday Costs 5 Pesos photograph negatives, October 7, 14, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - The Rivals photograph negatives, undated (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Tails Up photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Taming of the Shrew photograph negatives, May, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Taming of the Shrew photograph negatives, June, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Commencement program
  - Ten Nights in a Bar Room photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - This is What Happened photograph negatives, May 11 - 12, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Three Sisters photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Thunder Rock photograph negatives, March 20 - 21, April 10 - 11, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Tickless Time photograph negatives, March, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Tovarich photograph negatives, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Signals photograph negatives, March 6 - 7, 13 - 14, 21, May 1 - 2, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Signals photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - The Travellers photograph negatives, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Travelling Light photograph negatives, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Treasure Island photograph negatives, November 21, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Treasure Island photograph negative, November 21, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Treasure Island photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Trial by Jury photograph negatives, March 3 - 4, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Snow White and the 7 Dwarfs glass negatives, April 15 -16, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Two Blind Mice photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Two Gentlemen from Soho photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Under the Gaslight photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified glass negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Unidentified glass negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified glass negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified glass negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified glass negative, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Village Wooing photograph negatives, January 7 - 8, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Vinegar Tree photograph negatives, August 5 - 6, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - What a Life photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - While the Moon Grows Cold photograph negatives, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Why I am a Bachelor photograph negatives, February 11 - 12, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - The Wild Duck photograph negatives, April 1, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - The Wild Hills photograph negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Gard
  - Literature photograph negatives, November 7, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Cornell Dramatic Club one-act
  - Jubilee photograph negatives, November 7, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Windows photograph negatives, February 10 - 11, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 36)